是谁出主意让服务生都穿溜冰鞋的
So whose idea was it to put everybody in the diner on skates?
某个白痴客人投意见箱建议的
Some idiot customer put a suggestion in the suggestion box.
天啊  他们盗用我的点子
Oh, my God! They took my idea!
-居然是你  -对啊
- That was you? - Yeah.
行了  过去吧
Okay, there you go.
瑞秋  我帮你泡了可可
Rachel, I made you cocoa.
你好体贴...
Oh, that's so....
天啊  你们还好吗
Oh, my God! Are you guys okay?
辣喔
Oh, my.
你留山羊胡有点像撒旦
You know, with that goatee, you kind of look like Satan.
怪不得神父对我洒圣水
So that's why the priest threw holy water on me.
听着  你得振作一点  知道吗
Okay, listen, you have to cheer up! Okay?
你应该跟我和罗斯出门
You should come out with Ross and me.
总比整天坐在这里为凯特伤心好
Anything is better than sitting here crying all day about Kate.
我伤心是因为
I was crying because...
没有人相信昆西的理论
because nobody believed Quincy's theory.
我要上电视了
I'm gonna be on TV!
-不会吧  -真的
- No way! - Yeah.
有一个讨论秘鲁最新发掘化石的座谈会
They're putting together a panel to talk about the fossils in Peru.
探索频道要去拍摄
The Discovery Channel's filming it!
天啊  谁会看
Oh, my God! Who's gonna watch that?
-谢了  可以走了吗  -走吧
- Thanks. You ready to go? - Yeah.
-我看过一个女生穿那件背心  -多谢提醒
- I saw a girl with that vest. - Thanks.
大部分人视巧克力和礼篮为传统复活节礼物
Most of us think of chocolate and baskets as traditional Easter gifts.
有些人却坚持送活的小鸡
Some people insist on giving live chicks as presents.
告诉大家一个可悲的事实
Unfortunately, the sad fact remains
大部份的小鸡都活不到独立日
that most of these little guys won't live to see the fourth of July.
由于得不到妥善照顾  它们生命短暂
Because of as a result of improper care, they will be dead.
你们有小鸡吗
You guys got any of those baby chicks?
我看到电视上的广告
I was watching this commercial on TV,
天啊  那些小鸡好可爱哦
and man, those things are cute!
彼特  你回来了
Pete, you're back!
你看
Hey, check this out!
溜冰鞋
Skates!
你比钱德勒结实多了
You're sturdier than Chandler.
他一撞就散架
He crumbled like a piece of paper.
旅途顺利吗
How was your trip?
你送什么给我
What'd you bring me?
日本制造的宾馆化妆品
Hotel toiletries from Japan!
我会永远收藏好的
These are gonna go in my permanent collection.
-要喝咖啡吗  -当然  那最好不过了
- Want some coffee? - Yeah, sure, that'd be great.
普通的  还是低咖啡因的
Regular or decaf?
最近的就行了
Whichever's closest.
-问我今天做了什么  -你今天做了什么  彼特
- Ask me what I did today. - What did you do today, Pete?
我买下一家餐厅
I bought a restaurant
-想请你当主厨  -什么
- and I would like you to be the head chef. - What?
他居然要送我一家餐厅
Can you believe he offered me a restaurant?
真是个混蛋  你要我揍他吗
What a jerk. You want me to kick his ass?
从我拥有第一台烘烤箱
I mean this has been like my dream
开了莫家糕饼店开始  我的梦想便是拥有一家餐厅
since I got my first Easy Bake Oven andopened Easy Monica's Bakery.
有这份工作我死也甘愿  我绝对能胜任
I mean I would kill for this job. I can totally do this job...
上帝也知道  我吃的苦头也够多了
...and God knows, I've paid my dues.
但彼特这么做是因为他喜欢我
But Pete's doing this because he has a crush on me.
你对他还是没兴趣
And you're still not attracted to him at all?
没有
No.
我怎么能接受他的餐厅呢  不行
How could I accept a restaurant from him? I can't.
七年级时  史都·文森送我项链我都没收
I couldn't accept a necklace from Stu Vincent in the 7th grade.
但是莫妮卡  这是两回事
But, Mon, that was totally different.
他是你的健康教育老师
He was your health teacher.
怎么了  亲爱的
What, honey?
昨天被你撞到的地方还很痛
My side still hurts from when you crashed into me yesterday.
-天啊  对不起  -我知道
- Oh, God, I'm so sorry. - I know.
天啊
Oh, God!
嗨  你们猜怎样
Hey, you guys. Guess what?
你在邮轮上找到工作吗
Got a job on a riverboat?
就因为你不喜欢
Y'know what I didn't wear this suit for a year
我一整年没穿这套西装了
because you hated it. Well, guess what?
你不再是我的女朋友  所以...
You're not my girlfriend anymore,so....
我懂了  这身西装代表着
I see. This suit is making a point.
你现在孤家寡人
Now that you're on your own,
可以尽情地出丑
you're free to look as stupid as you'd like.
-你喜欢这套西装吧  -当然
- You like it, right? -  Oh absolutely.
你穿起来比肯德基爷爷还好看
I like it even more on you than I did on Colonel Sanders.
-罗斯  开玩笑的  -回来
- Ross, I'm kidding. - Come here.
你刚要说什么
What were you gonna tell us?
-你是如何发明轧棉机的吗  -再见
- Was it how you invented the cotton gin - Okay, goodbye.
你投书到意见箱之后多久
So after you put the suggestion in the box...
这个溜冰鞋的点子才得以实施
...how long did it take for the roll -skater thing to happen?
-大约三个月  -好吧
- About three months. - Okay.
所以离无上装的规定  大约还有两星期
So I guess that's about two weeks before the topless thing kicks in.
我给你买了份礼物
I got you something.
-打开来看  -好的
- Open it! Open it! - Okay.
是一只鸡
It's a chicken.
很可爱吧
It's cute, huh?
两位  你们了解鸡吗
You guys? Do you know anything about chicks?
家禽  不了解
Fowl? No.
女人  不了解
Women? No.
养鸡责任重大
They are a huge responsibility.
尤其是小鸡  他们需要有规律的照顾
Especially at this age. They require constant care.
它们不能吃错东西  需要很多关爱
They need just the right food and lots and lots of love.
这个没问题
Well,no problem there.
轻一点  鸡妈妈
Easy, Lenny.
你考虑过了吗
So, I mean, have you thought about it?
是这样的
Okay, here's the thing.
不要啊  我讨厌你说"是这样的"
No. Not "the thing." I hate "the thing."
是怎样的
What's "the thing"?
我不能接受
I can't do it.
抱歉  我也很想接受  但...
I'm sorry. I wish I could, but I...
所以你是喜欢我吧
So you have these feelings for me.
等等  等等  你在担心这个吗
Wait, wait, wait. That's what you're worried about?
如果是这个问题  那就没问题了
If that's the problem, we've got no problem.
不是这样的  我正打算吃饭时告诉你
No. I was gonna tell you over dinner,
我这趟出国认识了一个人
but I met somebody else, on my trip.
她叫安  是名记者
Her name's Ann. She's a journalist.
我们在飞机上认识的
We met on the plane.
她问我能否把我的花生吃完
She asked me if she could finish off my peanuts,
我听成别的  我们大笑一场
I thought she said something else. We had a big laugh.
我只是...受够了等待
Yeah, I just, I mean I got, I got tired of waiting.
太好了
That's great.
抱歉  但我十分为你高兴
I mean I'm-I'm sorry, but I'm so happy for you.
-现在我可以为你工作了  -看来可以了
- Now I can work for you! - I guess you can.
天啊  太棒了
Oh, my God! This is incredible!
好吧  等着
All right, y'know what?
我要溜进办公室去辞职
I'm gonna roll right into that office and quit!
好
All right!
-可以推我一下吗  -可以
-Could you give me a little push? - Yeah.
-祝你好运  -我要辞职了
- Good luck! - I'm quitting!
我没事  我很好
I'm okay! I'm all right!
真令人兴奋啊
That's exciting.
你去了趟日本  编造了个女人
You went to Japan, made up a woman.
什么
What?
我是说这个女人...是虚构的  不是吗
I'm just saying, this "woman," I mean, she's fictitious, no?
-为什么这么说  -你还是喜欢莫妮卡
- Why would you say that? - 'Cause you're still into Monica.
你谎称有了别人  好让她与你共事
You said there's somebody else so she would agree to work with you,
因为你觉得  如果相处久了
so 'cause you figure, if you spent a lot of time together,
也许就会产生感情
maybe something might happen, and...
你真行  你真行
You're good. You're good.
我只是直觉准  还会通灵
No, I'm fairly intuitive. And psychic.
很实在的天赋
It's a substantial gift.
听我说  你能答应我不要告诉她吗
Listen. Can you promise me that you won't tell her?
没问题  我答应你  告诉她什么
Absolutely. I promise. Tell her what?
谢谢你
Thanks a lot.
不  说真的
No, I'm serious.
虽然我的直觉很准  但记性很差
I mean I'm intuitive, but my memory sucks.
好吧  但这是最后一次
Okay, but this is the last time.
*这里有只小小鸡  那里有只小小鸡*
*With a chick-chick here And a chick-chick there*
*这只鸡  那只鸡  到处都有小小鸡*
*Here a chick, there a chick Everywhere a chick-chick*
鸡...
Chicken....
鸡妹妹好吗
How's she doing?
妹妹
She?
你不觉得是妹妹吗
Don't you think it's a she?
我不知道
I don't know.
看不出来  那个东西一下子就缩回去了
I can't tell. Whatever it was went back in too quickly.
我要换衣服
Anyway, I gotta change.
我要去跟其他演员喝酒
I'm meeting some of the cast for drinks.
-什么  -怎么了
- Excuse me? - What?
我今天在家呆了一天没上班
I stayed home from work today
好让你在排练时
while you were at rehearsal...
能有人陪着我们的小鸡
...so somebody could be here with our chick.
是谁从凌晨两点撑到凌晨五点
Who was up from 2:00 this morning until 5:00 this morning...
就为了要哄她睡觉
...trying to get her back to sleep?
你以为你起来时  我没醒着吗
You don't think I get up when you get up?
又来了
Oh, here it comes.
没错  又来了  我整天闷在家里
Yes! Here it comes! I'm stuck here all day!
你才回来跟我们呆了几秒钟
And then you come in and spend two seconds with us...
就要出去跟朋友花天酒地
...and then expect to go off gallivanting with your friends?
这样不行喔  先生
Well, I don't think so, mister!
我需要轻松一下  好吗  我忙了一整天
I need to relax, okay? I was working all day.
你觉得照顾我们的小鸡就不忙吗
And you don't think taking care of our chick is work?
我不是那个意思  好吗
That's not what I said, okay?
-我是说...  -我知道你想说什么
-  I just meant... - I know what you meant!
你有没有发现  自从有了小鸡
Did you notice that ever since we got this chick...
我们争吵的次数变多了
...we've been fighting a lot more than we used to?
谁知道  也许我们还没准备好养小鸡
I don't know, maybe we weren't ready to have a chick.
我明天送她回去
I'll take her back tomorrow.
那三块钱会退给我们吗
We'll get our $3 back?
我两小时后要录影  请你们帮个忙
Listen, I have that TV thing in two hours, and I need your help, ok?
怎么样  蓝色还是棕色的好
What do you think? This blue suit or this brown one?
棕色可以突显你的眼睛
The brown one brings out your eyes.
但蓝色那套  显得你的屁股很翘
But your butt looks great in the blue one.
真的吗
Really?
祈药舞还真有效
That aspirin dance really works.
-你还是...  -我没事  没事
- Anyway, is that still...? - I'm fine. I'm fine.
-你有事  -我没事
- No, you're not! - Yes, I am.
-瑞秋  -我很好  你瞧
-Rach. - Look, I'm fine. Watch. Look at that.
好啦  好啦
OK, okay, look.
你得去看医生  知道吗
You've got to go to a doctor, okay?
我要去我老板家参加晚宴
I have to get ready and go to a dinner at my boss's house.
这很重要  有几个人非见不可
Very big deal. There's people there that I have to meet.
你一定会令人印象深刻
I'm sure you'll make a great impression.
"你好  我是瑞秋·格林"
"Hi, I'm Rachel Greene.
"很高兴认识你"
It's nice to meet you."
别倔了  你的肋骨可能断了
Come on, you probably have a broken rib.
反正断都断了  我明天再去医院
I'll go to the hospital tomorrow. It'll still be broken then.
不过我打扮时的确需要人帮忙
But you know, I could use a hand getting ready.
-瑞秋  -你不帮忙就走
- Rachel. - Either help me, or go.
好  我走
Fine. I'll go.
走之前能不能先帮忙
Okay, but before you go, could you help me first?
当然  我帮你吧
Sure. I'll help you.
还好你们在
Good, good!
知道怎么把小鸡弄出录影机吗
Do you guys know how to get a chick out of a VCR?
光靠左手我化不了妆
You know what? I cannot do this with my left hand.
你能不能也帮下忙
Would you please help me with this too?
好吧
Ok.
-用这一支好了  -好
- Let's use this brush. - Okay.
-这个  -小心一点
- This stuff? - Careful.
沾一点
Light.
-在眼睑上刷一下就好  刷一下  -知道啦
- Just sweep it across the lid. Just sweep it. - Oke-dokey.
对不起
Sorry!
你是在戳我的眼睛
That's just poking me in the eye.
对不起  闭上...
I'm sorry. Close....
-刷就好  -我在刷
- Just sweep it. - I'm sweeping.
-好  -刷  刷
-All right. - Sweep, sweep....
-刷均匀  不要...  -什么
- Now make it even, because we don't.... - What?
不要太多  隐隐约约就好
You know what? I don't want it to be too much. I want it to be subtle.
不不  你的妆不够浓
No, no. You don't wear enough of this.
你什么时候开始觉得我的妆不够浓了
Since when do you think I don't wear enough of this?
闭上眼睛  你一定会喜欢这个新妆容
Close your eye. You're gonna like this better....
-闭眼睛  闭眼睛  -吹一下
- Close, close, close. - Blow it.
抱歉
Sorry.
因为我觉得这样看起来比较成熟
Because I think this will make you a little more sophisticated.
跟妓女一样成熟吗
Sophisticated like a hooker?
-你猜我今晚要做什么  -什么
- Guess what I'm doing tonight. - What?
我要跟彼特去看餐厅
I'm checking out the restaurant with Pete.
莫妮卡  我好替你开心
Monica, I am so excited for you!
我有一件事要告诉你
I have to tell you something.
什么事
What?
我不能告诉你
I can't tell you.
好吧  那你挑能告诉我的事情说不是更好吗
Okay. Wouldn't it be easier to tell me something that you could tell me?
是呀  哪有那么好的事情
Well, sure, in a perfect world.
可不行  我答应不说
But no. I promised I wouldn't tell,
我对所有神明发过誓
and I swore to all my Gods.
好吧
Okay.
-跟罗斯和瑞秋有关吗  -无关
- Does it have to do with Ross and Rachel? - No.
-跟乔伊有关吗  -无关
- Does it have to do with Joey? - No.
跟钱德勒和他床边的袜子有关吗
Does it have to do with Chandler and that sock he keeps by his bed?
不是  不过你等下你要给我讲讲
No, but let's come back to that later.
好了  参加晚宴够美了吧
There you go! Good enough for your party?
是啊
Sure.
是啊  我就坐在采购部那个人妖旁边吧
Sure. I'll just sit next to the transsexual from purchasing.
不要这样说嘛  好啦  起来吧
Come on. Okay, come on.
好了  我得走了  祝你晚宴愉快
All right, I gotta go, So good luck at the party.
等下  罗斯  再帮我换一下衣服可以吗
Wait. Ross, could you just stay and help me get dressed?
-没问题  -太好了
- Sure. Okay. - Okay, great.
-好的  转过去吧  -什么
- Okay, just turn around. - What?
我不想让你看到我的裸体
I don't want you to see me naked.
瑞秋  我都看过几万遍了
Rachel, I've seen you naked a million times.
我在你裸体上吃过热奶油
I ate hot fudge off you naked.
还从你的肚脐眼  吸出过小软糖呢
I sucked that mini-marshmallow out of your bellybutton.
那个不一样  我们那时在交往
Yeah, but that was different. I mean, we were, we were going out then,
现在很奇怪
now I think it's weird.
瑞秋  只要我想  我随时能看到你的裸体
Rach, you know, I can see you naked anytime I want.
什么
What?
我只需要闭上眼睛  你看
All I have to do is close my eyes. See?
罗斯  别闹了
Ross, stop that!
拜托  我不希望你以那种方式想我
Come on! I don't think of me like that anymore.
抱歉  你管不到
Sorry. Nothing you can do about it.
这是我身为前任男友的权利之一
It's one of my rights as the ex-boyfriend.
别闹了  够了  够了
Stop it! Cut it out! Cut it out!
好啦  对不起  我不会再...
Okay, I'm sorry. It will never happen
等一下
Wait a minute! Wait,wait....
现在有一百个你  我是国王
Now there are 100 of you, and I'm the king!
-罗斯  -拜托
- Ross. - Come on.
成熟一点  这又没什么
Would you grow up? It's no big deal.
够了  好吧
All right. Fine.
这下你满意了吧  我自己换衣服算了
See what you did? I'm gonna be doing it by myself now.
如何  真是够了
Okay? That's it.
天啊  听我说
Oh, my God. All right, look, look....
瑞秋  小心  慢点
Rach. Easy. Easy.
你得去医院  好吗
You have to go to the hospital, okay?
我真得去了
I do. I really do.
-那我去帮你拿外套  再送你上车  -好
- Okay, I'll get your coat, then I'll put you in a cab. - Okay.
你不陪我去吗
You're not gonna come with me?
当然陪你
Of course I am.
我得先打个电话  可以吗
I just have to make a call, okay?
谢谢
Thank you.
怎么了
What's wrong?
对不起  我不能这样去医院
I'm sorry. I just can't go to the hospital looking like this.
-跟旅行有关吗  -没有
- Does it involve travel? - No.
跟木屐有关吗
Does it involve clogs?
等等  木屐还是爪子
Wait. Clogs or claws?
-木屐  -不
- Clogs. - No.
-爪子  -也不是
- Claws? - No.
所以不是罗斯和瑞秋
Okay. So it doesn't involve Ross or Rachel
也不是钱德勒和乔伊
or Chandler or Joey.
-那彼特呢  -不是
- What about Pete? - No
怎么回事
What is it?
-彼特怎么了  -我不知道
- What about Pete? - I don't know!
我好像在跟灵犬莱西说话
Okay, I feel like I'm talking to Lassie.
-菲比  你就直说好吗  -不行啦
- Phoebe, would you just tell me? - I can't!
-好吧  我得走了  -但你很接近了
- Okay, I gotta go. - But you're so close!
是跟彼特的电脑公司有关吗
Okay, does it involve something to do with Pete's computer company?
你走吧  你死也猜不到的
Go! You'll never get it!
我知道
I know.
没错  那就是雅丝敏·布丽丝
See, yes. That's Yasmine Bleeth.
她是一种完全不同的"品种"
She's a completely different kind of chick.
你们两个我都爱
I love you both.
是非常不一样的爱
But in very different ways.
你在干什么  不是说今天要送她回商店吗
What are you doing? You were gonna take her back to the store today.
我有送  但是店里不收
I did. But the store wouldn't take her back.
后来我带她去收容所  你猜我发现什么
Then I took her to the shelter. You know what I found out?
要是找不到人领养就要杀了她
If they can't find a home for her, they kill her!
我绝不让小雅丝敏惨遭毒手
I won't let that happen to little Jasmine.
很好  很好
Okay, good, good, good,
-其实后来我也有点反悔  -好
- 'cause, good, 'cause I was kinda having second thoughts too. - Okay.
不只小鸡
And it's not just chicks, you know?
所有的动物都一样
It's all kinds of other animals.
太可怕了  你做得对
That's horrible. You did the right thing.
谢了  你这么想就好
Thanks. I'm glad you see it that way.
说来好笑
Funny story!
真不敢相信
I don't believe this!
你看这个冰柜  有够大的
Look at this refrigerator! It's gigantic!
我都可以住在里面
I could live in this thing!
虽然会冷  不过我本来就很冷
I'd be cold, but I'm always cold!
天啊  是传统火炉
Oh, my God! Look at these spider burners!
我最喜欢传统火炉了
I love spider burners!
你喜欢喽
So you like it?
太完美了  真谢谢你
It is so perfect! Thank you so much.
不客气
You're welcome.
你刚才在闻我的头发吗
Did you just smell my hair?
怎么可能  没有啊
No! No way! What?
-天啊  -怎么了
-Oh, God. -What?
你对我还是有感觉  是吧
You still have feelings for me don't you?
不  我只是对餐厅的事很兴奋
No, I'm just excited about the restaurant, that's all.
-彼特  -好吧  我爱你  有这么糟吗
- Pete. - OK, I love you. Is that so bad?
不糟  一点也不糟
No, it's not bad. It's not bad at all.
其实很好
It's really nice.
我们两个人中会受伤的人是我
The only one who stands to get hurt is me,
我都不介意了
and I'm okay with that.
你或许不介意受伤
You may be okay with getting hurt...
但我却不能当那个伤你的人
but I am not okay with being the one who hurts you.
-所以我不能接受这份工作  -什么
- That's why I can't take this job. - What?
我们或许也不该再见面了
We probably shouldn't see each other anymore.
对不起
I'm sorry.
那好吧
Okay.
你如果真的这么想  那好吧
I mean, if that's really what you want, okay.
很抱歉事情...
I'm sorry things
你先闭嘴  让我确认一下
Shut up for a second and let me just see something.
你有说实话吗
You'd tell me the truth?
瑞秋  X光片看起来怎么会胖
Rach, you can't look fat in an x-ray.
你给我在这里好好反省
Now you stay out here and you think about what you did!
-那是一只鸭子  -一只坏鸭子
- That's a duck! - That's a bad duck!
今晚的事顺利吗  罗斯
How'd the thing go tonight, Ross?
什么事  什么事
What thing? What thing?
没什么  就是博物馆有点事  走吧
Nothing. There was this thing at the museum. Come on.
小心
Easy.
等放你回来的时候  我要你记住
Ok, Now, when you come back, I hope you remember that
鸡妹妹不是玩具
that chick is not a toy!
什么事  到底是什么事
What "thing"? What is this "thing"?
我今晚本来要上探索频道的节目
I was kind of supposed to be on TV tonight for the Discovery Channel.
天啊
Oh, my God!
罗斯  你为什么不说
Ross, why didn't you tell me that?
我知道我一说你就会赶我去
I knew that if I told you, you'd make me go...
而你今晚需要有人陪同  来吧
...and I knew you needed someone to be with you tonight. Come on.
-我真不敢相信  -什么
- I cannot believe you. - What?
你对我太好了
That is the sweetest thing.
你该睡觉了
You should get some sleep.
抱歉搞砸你的计划
Sorry I spoiled your evening.
你没事就好
As long as you're okay.
明天见
So I'll see you tomorrow.
再见
See you.
你犯了什么错
What did you do?
你们在干什么
What you doing?
游泳
Having a swim.
鸡妹妹呢
What about the chick?
鸡不会游泳
Chicks don't swim.
你确定吗
Are you sure?
不晓得
I don't know.
-要试试看吗  -好啊
- Should we try? - Sure.
看吧  我就说它不会游
See, I told you. They don't swim.
-再等一下  -那怎么行
-Well, give him a minute. - No.
乖  没事了  没事了  宝贝
It's okay. It's okay, baby, baby, baby.